information = [
    {

        "question": "Sanskrit is the Oldest Language in the World",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {

        "question": "There are approx 500 languages in the World",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {

        "question": "Malayalam is a Palindrome",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {

        "question": "Most number of languages are spoken in Europe Continent ",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {

        "question": "According to Forbes Magazine,Sanskrit is the most computer-friendly Language",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {

        "question": "Hindi is the 2nd most spoken language in the world ",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {

        "question": "Half of the Languages in the World have no written form",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {

        "question": "Many tribal languages in India do not face extinction threat",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {

        "question": "Sanskrit is the mother of all languages",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {

        "question": "English has borrowed a great number of words from Hindi",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    }
]
